Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) photograph series D (faculty and staff portraits), 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series D, Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - M
    - McPherson, Mrs., 1973 (Box 9)
    - McQueen, Albert, Sociology; Research Center for Group Dynamics, 1964 (Box 9)
    - McVaugh, Rogers, Botany; University Herbarium, 1958, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Meares, Paula Allen, Social Work, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Medaugh, Marlyn, Human Nutrition Program (School of Public Health), 1974 (Box 9)
    - Medders, Mardy, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Mednick, Sarnoff, Psychology, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Meecham, William C., Physics, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Meier, Gitta, Maternal and Child Health, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Meier, Gustav, Music, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Meier, Richard L., School of Natural Resources; MHRI, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Meikle, Herbert G., English Language Institute, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Meinke, W. Wayne, Chemistry, 1957 (Box 9)
    - Meisel, James H., Political Science, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Meisels, Samuel, Center for Human Growth, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Meitus, Irving J., Speech, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Melchiori, Gerlond S., Academic Planning and Analysis, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Mellett, Lawrence B., Pharmacology, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Meloche, Clifford C., Chemistry, 1955 (Box 9)
      (na 855)
    - Melton, Arthur, Psychology, 1964, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Mendenhall, George E., Near Eastern Studies, 1965 (Box 9)
    - Mendler, Janet, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Menefee, Ferdinand N., 1955 (Box 9)
    - Menlo, Allen, Education, 1957, 1977, 1984, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Merchant, Donald J., Bacteriology, 1960, 1968 (Box 9)
    - Merhab, William G., Education; Romance Languages; Modern Languages; University School, 1961, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Merker, Harvey M., 1951 (Box 9)
      (na 857)
    - Merlin, Roberto, Physics, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Mersereau, John, Jr., Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Merte, Herman, Jr., Mechanical Engineering, 1960, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Merten, Alan, Business Administration, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Messick, Brinkley, Anthropology, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Messiter, Arthur F., Institute for Science and Technology; Aeronautical and Astronautical Engineering, 1962, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Metcalf, Robert C., Architecture, 1965, 1985, 1976, 1970, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Metivier, Lionel, Education, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Metton, Carl, Surgery, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Metzelaar, Lena, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Metzer, Kurt, EECS, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Metzner, Charles A., Public Health Economics, 1957, 1963 (Box 9)
      (na 858)
    - Metzner, Helen, Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Meyer, Alfred, 1967, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Meyer, Henry J., Social Work; Sociology, 1959, 1962 (Box 9)
      (nb 503)
    - Meyer, John F., Computer Engineering; Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1975, 1986, 1971, 1969, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Meyer, Richard D., PTP; Speech communication and Theater, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Meyer, Suzanne (Mrs. Henry J.), Human Relations; Office of Student Affairs, 1962 (Box 9)
      (nb 504)
    - Meyers, Phil, Atmospheric and Oceanic Science, 1984, 1979, 1987, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Meyers, Steve, Housing E.O.M., 1989 (Box 9)
    - Meyers, Vernon, ROTC, 1965 (Box 9)
    - Michael, Donald N., Psych.; Natural Resources; Center for Research on Util of Sci Knowl; ISR, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Micheels, Barbara, Mus., 1976 (Box 9)
    - Michelsen, Finn C., Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Miedler, Leo J., Industrial Health, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Miesel, Victor H., History of Art, 1961, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Mignolo, Walter, Romance Languages, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Milholland, John E., Psych., 1955 (Box 9)
    - Millar, Kenneth, 1953 (Box 9)
    - Miller (Box 9)
    - Miller, (Vanderhaggen) Anita, Donor Relations, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Arthur, Law, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Arthur, Hopwood, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Edwin L., Industrial Relations, 1966, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Harry E., Public Health Engineering and Sanitation, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Henry W., Engineering Drawing, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Herbert E., Accounting, 1957 (Box 9)
    - Miller, James K., Development Council, 1965 (Box 9)
    - Miller, James L., Education, 1988, 1969, 1975, 1978, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Janice D., International Center, 1958, 1959 (Box 9)
      (na 862)
    - Miller, Merlin W., Registration and Records, 1958 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Murray H., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Miller, N. Edd, Speech (Box 9)
    - Miller, Norman F., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1953 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Pat, Urban Planning, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Robert R., Zoology, 1966, 1950 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Seward E., Institute of Industrial Health; Medical School; School of Public Health, 1958 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Warren E., Political Science; ISR; Interuniversity Consortium of Political Research, 1957, 1969 (Box 9)
      (na 863)
    - Mills, Carolyn, Psychology, Dearborn, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Mills, George E., Bureau of School Services, 1965, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Mills, Harriett, Far Eastern Languages, 1967, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Mills, Robert H., School of Business Administration, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Mills, William H., University School; Education, 1965, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Milne, Robert C., Extension Services, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Milone, Nicholas, Environmental Health, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Mims, Sue, Academic Planning and Analysis, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Miner, Horace M., Sociology; Anthropology, 1954 (Box 9)
    - Minihan, J., HSRI, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Minuse, Elva, Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Miracle, Gordon E., School of Business Administration, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Mirageas, Evans J., WUOM, 1979, 1980, 1981, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Mirsky, William, Mechanical Engineering, 1965, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Misko, Aloysius E., Inservice Training Program; Personnel Office, 1959, 1960 (Box 9)
      (nb 509)
    - Mitani, John, Anthropology, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Mitchell, Bede, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Mitchell, Elmer D., Physical Education, 1958, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Mitchell, Jack, WUOM, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Moe, Nancy, Naval Science, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Moerman, Daniel, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Moffett, James W., U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service (Box 9)
    - Mohler, John D., Music, 1962, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Mohler, Orren C., Astronomy; McMath-Hulbert Observatory, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Mohr, Lawrence, Public Administration, 1968 (Box 9)
    - Mohring, Herbert G. (Box 9)
    - Moise, Edwin E., Mathematics, 1953 (Box 9)
      (na 868)
    - Molin, Keith, Development Office, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Moll, Russell, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Moller, William G., Jr., Bureau of Business Relations; School of Business Administration, 1967, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Moltrecht, Karl H., Mechanical Engineering, 1958 (Box 9)
    - Momot, Walter, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Monahan, Edward C., Dr., Sea Grant, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Moncrieff, Fred, News Service, 1964, 1965, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Monterio, Anne W., Engineering Administration, 1983, 1978, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Montgomery, Bruce, Natural Sciences, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Montgomery, Hugh, Mathematics, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Montgomery, Susan M., Chemical Engineering, 1992, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Monto, Arnold, School of Public Health, 1965, 1975, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Montoya, Maria, History, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Montoye, Henry J., Physical Education for Men; School of Public Health, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Monts, Lester, Office of Academic Affairs, 1993, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Moody, Charles, South African Initiative Office; Vice Provost for Minority Affairs; School of Education, 1993, 1988, 1995, 1977, 1973, 1983, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Mook, Dean T., Engineering Mechanics, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Moore, A. D., Electrical Engineering, 1949, 1950, 1960 (Box 9)
      (na 872-874)
    - Moore, C. N., 1953 (Box 9)
      (na 875)
    - Moore, Daniel, Audio-Visual Center, 1957 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Earl V., Music (Box 9)
    - Moore, Felix, Biostatistics, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Frank, School of Business Administration, 1965, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Rosalie I., Naval Science, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Ted C., Center for Great Lakes & Acquatic Sciences, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Thomas E., Zoology, 1966, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Moos, Malcolm, 1955 (Box 9)
      (na 879)
    - Moran, William E., UM Flint College, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Moravcsik, Julius, Philosophy, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Moreno, Irene, English Language Lab., 1953 (Box 9)
      (na 882)
    - Morgan, Ginnie, 1956 (Box 9)
      (na 883)
    - Morgan, James N., Economics; Survey Research Center, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Morgan, Robert, Alumni Association, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Morley, Arthur, Naval Science, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Morley, D. E., Speech; Speech Clinic; School of Education, 1960, 1975, 1951, 1964 (Box 9)
      (na 881, nb 516)
    - Morley, Helen Joan, Speech Clinic; Speech, 1964, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Morris, Aldon, LS&A (Box 9)
    - Morris, Charles, Psychology; LSA, 1971, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Morris, Donald A., University Relations, 1962, 1965 (Box 9)
      (nb 517)
    - Morris, E. A. (Jack) (Box 9)
    - Morris, Michael, Chemistry, 1996, 1995, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Morris, Sandra (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 9)
    - Morrison, Richard B., Aeronautical Engineering, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Morrison, Richard B. or Roger L., Richard B.: Engineering Research Institute; Roger L.: Engineering and Highway Transport; Transportation Library, 1949 (Box 9)
      (na 886)
    - Morrissey, Mary C., Student (Box 9)
    - Morse, William C., Educational Psychology; Fresh Air Camp; School of Education, 1948, 1960, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Morton, Harrison L., Natural Resources, 1967, 1980, 1978, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Mosca, Lori, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Moser, Thomas, Speech, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Moses, David, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Moses, Harry, Oceanography and Meteorology, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Mosher, Eliz, Music (Box 9)
    - Mosher, Raymond F., Electrical Engineering, 1960, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Moss, Thylias, English, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Mothersill, Philip W., Naval Science, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Motora, Seizo, Institute of Science and Technology, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Mott, Paul E., Sociology, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Mottl, Thomas O., Electrical Engineering, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Moulton, Robert, Bureau of Psychological Services, 1955 (Box 9)
    - Mourou, Gerard, Engineering, 1998, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Mouw, David R., Physiology, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Mouzon, James Carlisle, Engineering; Willow Run, 1966 (Box 9)
      (nb 519, na 891)
    - Moyer, R. S., Dentistry (Box 9)
    - Mrazek, Rudolf, 2006 (Box 9)
    - Mrowa, Dounia J., 1951 (Box 9)
      (na 891)
    - Muehl, Doris O., Survey Research Center, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Muehl, John, English, 1951, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Mueller, August, Conference Dept., 1972, 1969, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Mueller, Eva, Institute for Social Research; Economics, 1955, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Mueller, Floran, Music, 1954 (Box 9)
    - Mueller, Gus, Extension Service, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Mueschke, English, 1957 (Box 9)
    - Mueschke, Mrs., Russian, 1957 (Box 9)
    - Muir, Roy E., 1984 (Box 9)
    - Mulder, Harlan, VP & Chief Financial Officer, 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Mulder, Jerry, State and Community Relations, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Mulford, Robert, 1950 (Box 9)
      (na 892)
    - Mullen, Albert P., Art, 1957, 1963 (Box 9)
      (na 894)
    - Muller, Robert H., University Libraries, 1963, 1969, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Muller, Robert O., 1969 (Box 9)
    - Mullet, Garry, Business Administration, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Munn, Cheryl, Administrative Systems Planning (Box 9)
    - Munro, Donald J., Philosophy, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Munson, Fred C., Business Administration, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Murnan, James D., Lydia Mendelssohn Theater (Box 9)
    - Murphey, Rhodes, Geography; Center for Chinese Studies, 1968, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Murphy, Allan, Meteorology, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Murphy, Irene, Regent, 1962, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Murphy, Melbourne, Public Health Administration, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Murphy, Robert, Basketball (Box 9)
    - Murphy, William E., Physical Education, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Murray, Belle F., Parent Education, Extension Service, 1956 (Box 9)
    - Murray, Frank, School of Natural Resources, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Murray, James, Engineering Mechanics, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Murty, Katta G., Industrial and Op. Engineering, 1969, 1978, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Muschenheim, William, Architecture, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Musgrave, Richard A., Economics, 1957 (Box 9)
      (na 914)
    - Muyskens, John H., Speech, 1951 (Box 9)
      (na 915)
    - Myers, Alison, Alumni Association, 1969, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Myers, Sumner B., 1949 (Box 9)
      (na 918)
  - N
    - Naaman, Antonine E., Civil Engineering, 1983, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Nace, George W., Zoology, 1961, 1976, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Nadelman, Lorraine, Psychology, 1965, 1985, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Naessens, Marian, WUOM, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Nagel, Louis, Music, 1986, 1987, 1985, 1976, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Nagely, Donna, Counseling Services, 1975, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Naghdi, Paul M., Mechanical Engineering, 1956 (Box 9)
    - Nagy, Andrew F., Electrical Engineering, 1963, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Nagy, Andrew F., Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Najafi, Khalil, Engineering, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Nalecz, Andrew, Mechanical Engineering, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Napier, John A., Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Nary, Bruce L., Spanish, 1957 (Box 9)
    - Naylor, Arch W., UMRI, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Neal, Fred, 1953 (Box 9)
    - Neal, Homer, Physics, 1993, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Nederlander, Robert E., Regent, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Needham, Roger A., Institute of Continuing Legal Education; Law School, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Needler, Martin C., Political Science, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Neel, James, Human Genetics, 1985, 1970, 1966 (Box 9)
      (na 923)
    - Neenan, William, Economics and Social Work, 1978, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Neff, Franklin W., Survey Research Center, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Neidhardt, Frederick C., Medical School, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Neihuss, Marvin, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Nelson, Alexander, Bureau of School Services; School of Education, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Nelson, Geneva C., Music; Education, 1961, 1962 (Box 9)
      (na 924)
    - Nelson, Lyle, Journalism; University Relations (Box 9)
    - Nelson, Norman E., English, 1946 (Box 9)
      (na 927)
    - Nelson, Roger B., University Hospital, 1959 (Box 9)
      (na 928)
    - Nelson, Wilbur C., Aeroengineering, 1969 (Box 9)
      (na 929)
    - Nesbit, Reed M., Surgery, 1951, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Nesbitt, Cecil J., Mathematics, 1959, 1967, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Ness, Grayl, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Neu, Susan H., Student Education (Box 9)
    - Newburgh, L. H., Clinical Investigation (Box 9)
    - Newby, Stephen, Music, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Newcomb, Theodore, Sociology and Psychology, 1965, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Newcomb, Theodore M., 1948 (Box 9)
    - Newcomb, William K., School of Architecture; Natural Resources, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Newell, Barbara, 1968 (Box 9)
    - Newland, Leonard, HSRI, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Newman, Harry, Business Administration, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Newman, Joseph W., Business Administration, 1965, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Newman, Sandra, ISR, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Ni, Jun, Mechanical Engineering and Applied Mechanics, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Nibley, Reid M., Music, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Nicholls, James A., Aerospace Engineering, 1969, 1964, 1971, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Nichols, Myron H., Aeronautical Engineering, 1958 (Box 9)
      (na 932)
    - Niehuss, Lois, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Niehuss, Marvin L., Law; Vice President of the University, 1964, 1948, 1949, 1951, 1955, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Niess, Robert J., French, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Nietschmann, Bernard Q., Geography, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Nilsen, Don, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Nisbet, Ken, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Nisbett, Richard, Psychology, 1991, 1992, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Noehren, Robert, Music, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Noffsinger, Mark G., Office of Dean of Men, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Nolan, Elizabeth, Nursing, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Nolte, Loren, Electrical Engineering, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Nordby, Virginia, Exec. Asst. to the President; Affirmative Action Programs; Academic Affairs; School of Education; Vice President of Academic Affairs, 1984, 1986, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Nordin, Virginia, Institute of Continuing Legal Education, 1968, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Nordman, Christer E., Chemistry, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Norich, Anita, English, 1988, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Norman, A. Geoffrey, Vice President for Research; Botanical Gardens; Botany, 1964, 1967, 1968, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Norman, Richard, Architecture and Design, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Norman, Warren T., Psychology, 1966, 1961, 1979, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Norris, Mary Jane M., English Language Institute, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Norris, William E., English Language Institute, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Northrop, Robert M., Public Health Administration, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Norton, Hugh Z., Speech, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Novak, Jim, Extension Services, 1976 (Box 10)
    - Novy, Frederick, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Nowacki, Horst, Naval Architecture, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Nowak, Andrzej, Civil Engineering, 1997, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Nugent, Anita, Capital Planning, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Nurse, Esrold, LS&A, 1995 (Box 10)
  - O
    - Oakes, Edith, Public Health Nursing and Medical Care, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Oakley, Bruce, Biology, 1966, 1975, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Oakley, Deborah, School of Public Health, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Obenshain, W. A., 1966 (Box 10)
    - Oberdick, Willard A., Architecture, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Ocker, Phyllis, Physical Education, 1971 (Box 10)
    - O'Connor, Patricia, Maternal and Child Health, 1963, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Odegaard, Charles E., 1963, 1969 (Box 10)
    - O'Dell, William W., Jr., Engineering Mechanics, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Odiorne, George, Industrial Relations; Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Odom, Selma L., Dance, Physical Education Dept., 1972 (Box 10)
    - O'Donnell, Charles R., English, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Ogilvie, Francis R., Naval Architecture, 1967 (Box 10)
    - O'Keefe, Barbara, School of Information; Media Union, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Oksenberg, Michel C., Political Science and Chinese Studies, 1976, 1981 (Box 10)
    - O'Leary, James, French, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Olencki, Edward V., Architecture, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Oliver, Fred, Financial Analysis, 1957, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Oliver, William, Pediatrics Dept., 1967 (Box 10)
    - Olken, Ilene, Italian, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Olmsted, Charles T., Engineering Mechanics, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Olrich, Thomas M., Anatomy; Museum of Paleontology, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Olsen, Marvin P., 1967 (Box 10)
    - Olson, Charles E. Jr., Natural Resources, 1965, 1989, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Olson, Wilbur (Box 10)
    - Olson, Willard C., School of Education; Psychology, 1949, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Olsson, Gunnar P., Geography, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Olsson, Lars (Box 10)
    - Olte, Andrejs, Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Olving, Gerhard, Architecture, 1965, 1973 (Box 10)
    - O'Malley, Michael, Communication Science; Phonetics Lab, 1972 (Box 10)
    - O'Malley, Patric M., ISR (Box 10)
    - Oncley, J. Lawrence, Biophysics Research Div., 1972 (Box 10)
    - O'Neill, Fitzhugh, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Ong, Rudi, Aeronautical Engineering, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Oppenheim, S. C., Law, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Oppermann, Peter, Architecture, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Orbach, Harold L., Division of Gerontology; Institute for Human Adjustment, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Orbeck, Martin J., Engineering, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Orlin, Louis L., Ancient Near Eastern History and Literature, 1965, 1972, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Ormondroyd, Jesse, Engineering Mechanics, 1960 (Box 10)
    - O'Roke, Earl, Forestry, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Ortner, Sherry, Anthropology, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Osborn, June, School of Public Health, 1989 (Box 10)
    - Osborn, Richard K., Nuclear Engineering, 1960 (Box 10)
    - O'Shields, Chief G. R., Naval Science, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Ostafin, Peter A., Housing; Sociology, 1952 (Box 10)
    - Ostrand, Lillian, Public Health Nursing, 1963, 1973, 1977, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Oswald, Lynda, School of Business Administration, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Outcalt, Sam, Geography, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Overberger, Charles G., Vice President for Research; Chemistry, 1978, 1980, 1985, 1966, 1971, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Overmire, Thomas G., Academy of Science, Arts, and Letters, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Overseth, Anneke, Development Office; School of Business Administration, 1972, 1973, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Owen, Charles, Music, 1973, 1974, 1977, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Owen, Robert M., Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Owens, James, Aeronautical Engineering, 1963 (Box 10)
  - P
    - Pancoast, Katherine (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 10)
    - Parravano, Giuseppe, Chemical Engineering, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Partment, Lila, 1952 (Box 10)
      (na 2840)
    - Pasquariello, Anthony, Romance Languages, 1955 (Box 10)
    - Pastalan, Leon, Architecture, 1976, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Patchen, Martin, Survey Research Center, Psych., 1960, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Patno, Mary Ellen, Biostatistics, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Paton, William Sr., Accounting, Economics, 1961, 1953, 1951, 1969 (Box 10)
      (na 2842)
    - Patronsky, Louis A., 1952 (Box 10)
      (na 2841)
    - Patterson, Brenda, WUOM, 1979, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Patterson, James, Career Planning and Placement, 1976 (Box 10)
    - Patterson, Phyliss, Nursing, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Patterson, Willis, Music, 1968, 1975, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Paul, Ara, Chemistry, College of Pharmacy, 1968, 1974, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Paulson, Clarice, DSC, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Payne, Beverly C., Internal Medicine, 1963, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Payne, Francis E., Epidemiology, 1963, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Payne, Millicent, Epidemiology, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Peacor, Donald R., Geology and Minerology, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Peak, Helen, Psychology, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Peake, Charles, LSA, 1946 (Box 10)
      (na 2843-2844)
    - Pealy, Dorothee S., School of Business Administration, 1963, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Pealy, Robert H., Political Science, 1963, 1953, 1966 (Box 10)
      (na 2845)
    - Pearce, Donald R., 1950 (Box 10)
      (na 2846-2849)
    - Pearce, Jack R., Law, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Pearl, O. M., Greek, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Pearson, Chester E., University Hospital, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Pearson, Clarence F., Extension Service, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Pearson, Delbert E., Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Pearson, J. Raymond, Engineering, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Pearson, John, Naval Science, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Pearson, Ross N., Geography, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Pearson, Will, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Pease, Esther, Physical Education for Women, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Peckham, Howard, Clements Library, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Peek, George A., Political Science, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Pehlke, Robert D., Chemical Engineering, 1960, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Pellerito, Peter, State and Community Relations, 1985, 1987, 1989, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Pelletier, Charles, Environmental Health, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Pelz, Donald C., Survey Research Center, 1962, 1967 (Box 10)
      (nb 911-915, na 2854, na 2852-2853)
    - Pelz, Edith, Psychology, 1967, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Pena, Deagelia M. P., Affirmative Action, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Peng, Ming-min, Law School, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Penix, Findlay, Education, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Penner, John A., Internal Medicine, 1967, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Pennington, Anthony J., Electrical Engineering, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Penzl, Herbert, German, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Perakis, Anastassios, Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Perez, Simon, Romance Languages, 1961 (Box 10)
      (nb 916-918)
    - Perigo, Donald J., Orientation, 1978, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Perkins, Al, Music, 1976 (Box 10)
    - Perkins, Dave, University Press, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Perkins, John A., 1949 (Box 10)
    - Perlmutter, Marion, Gerontology, 1985 (Box 10)